http://www.massmutual.com/legal/cyber-security

Cyber Security
At MassMutual, we understand that you want to protect what matters most. One of the ways we can help is by ensuring that your personal information is kept confidential and secure. MassMutual takes cyber security seriously, continuously investing in tools, resources and personnel that help us keep that commitment. Our information security team monitors risk factors every day so that personal data, and the systems that manage it, are safe.
Report an information security concern
If you are concerned about the security of the information you have entrusted to us, or have received a suspicious email or telephone call claiming to be from us, we want to hear from you.
How we protect your information
We help people secure their future and protect the ones they love. As part of this purpose, cyber security is incorporated into our business practices upfront. MassMutual continuously invests in an Enterprise Information Risk Management Program consisting of written Information Technology Policies and Standards that are designed to safeguard the security, confidentiality, integrity, and availability of personal information in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. These measures were developed in accordance with leading industry guidelines and best practices. Our Program and our Standards provide a framework for managing risks associated with MassMutual’s information technology resources and mechanisms to identify, assess, and monitor risks to nonpublic personal information.
MassMutual takes cyber security seriously and we’ll continue to make investments that help protect both customer and employee information. This includes providing the right personnel and resources to our dedicated Information Risk Management Program that is aligned with leading industry guidelines.
We truly value the trusting relationships we have built and believe we need to continue to earn that trust every day, for new and existing clients. One of the ways we do that is by staying committed to protecting the information entrusted to us and continuously investing in that commitment.
Read More
How We Use Your Information
The information we collect helps us deliver more targeted services, products, and educational tools to help you reach your financial goals. Our Privacy Policy further explains how we use your information.
Privacy Policy on Collecting and Using Personal Information
Information Security Statement on Practices and Policies
Resources to help secure personal data
We’re all in this together. Learn how you can take steps to protect your identity, your financial information and your online activity by visiting these well-known resources.
Q: What can I do if I suspect someone has stolen my personal information?
A: If you suspect that your personal information has been compromised, learn how to recover from acts of identity theft at the Federal Trade Commission Identity Theft Center.
Q: Where can I learn how to spot fraudulent emails and websites?
A: The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission can teach you how to identify phishing emails and fake websites and the U.S. Department of Homeland Security can help you protect yourself from getting caught in online scams.
Q: How do I monitor my credit and credit score?
A: You can request a free credit report every 12 months at AnnualCreditReport.com and review all the items that affect your financial life.
Q: What are the basic steps I can take to protect my financial information?
A: A breach of your financial information can lead to having your identity stolen. The Financial Industry Regulatory Authority (FINRA) has compiled a summary of steps you can take to spot potential online threats and protect your personal information and financial accounts.
Tips for Staying Safe Online
Creating Secure Passwords
5 Measures for Mobile Device Security
Tips to Help Spot a Phishing Scam
Practice Safe Web Browsing
Social Networking Safety Guidelines
Report an Information Security Concern
If you are concerned about the security of the information you have entrusted to us, or have received a suspicious email or telephone call claiming to be from us we want to hear from you.
Contact Us
Get the latest insurance, retirement, and financial planning news.
Our newsletter provides insights into current events, financial tactics and ways to save.
©2020 Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance Company (MassMutual®), Springfield, MA 01111-0001. All rights reserved.
Sitemap
Terms of Use
Privacy
CRN999999
